

# **MUHAMAD RAFFI**

FRONTEND DEVELOPMENT | BELAJARSAMPAITUNTAS.BLOGSPOT.COM |

## **OBJECTIVE**

I am interested and passionate about programming. I've known IT since I was in Vocational high school. I'm currently taking diploma level 4 at the state polytechnic of batam, I also have experience in the field of basic networking and IT support for 6 month at it center BP batam. And I also have 1 year of proggraming learning experience.

#### SKILLS

 I'm dominate at now is basic javascript, html, and css. I also mastered the basics of c, and also mastered the basics of networking.

### **EXPERIENCE**

**NETWORKING • IT CENTER BP BATAM • JULI 2017 – NOVEMBER 2017** Troubleshooting networking and LAN, Helpdesk, office application, instalasi software, and Assembly & disassembly computer.

**CONTENT CREATOR • YOUTUBE • OCTOBER 2018 – PRESENT**Create content about all the knowledge that I learn online then put it in the video

#### **EDUCATION**

MULTIMEDIA AND NETWORKING • SEPTEMBER 2020 - PRESENT • BATAM STATE POLYTECHNIC – BATAM

data structures, responsive web design, algorithms and programming, databases, computer networks.

COMPUTER AND NETWORK ENGINEERING • 2016 - 2019 • MUHAMMADIYAH VOCATIONAL HIGH SCHOOL 1 BATAM

OS installation, computer repair, LAN repair installation, WAN repair installation, mikrotik server administration, create simple web. learn server administration.

### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE OR LEADERSHIP**

Become chairman branch martial arts tapak suci putera muhammadiyah at muhammadiyah vocational high school — chairman branch — 2017 - 2019







